First Last

Automation Tester

Quality-focused automation tester with 8 years of experience in web and mobile app testing. Proven ability to find and isolate defects through comprehensive exploratory testing. Key achievement: Overhauled 5 UI automated testing solutions leading to a dramatic 89% increase in test traceability and overall product quality.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Automation Tester

November 2015 - Present

Resume Worded, New York, NY

- Automated manual test cases using Selenium WebDriver and Python to improve the efficiency of testing by 92%.
- Reported and tracked software defects using bug-tracking tools and assisted with root cause analysis, resolved 75% of issues discovered.
- Overhauled 5 UI automated testing solutions leading to a dramatic 89% increase in test traceability and overall product quality.
- Tested 15 versions of RW's software taking account of unique geographical terrain and 10 browser platforms, achieved an 85% product useability rate.

Information Security Analyst

June 2013 - October 2015

Growthsi, San Francisco, CA

- Analyzed system logs, network traffic, and 15 other digital footprints to detect unauthorized access attempts, prevented >2K malicious attacks in Q1 2014 alone.
- Created an automated tool that allowed over 10K users to submit requests for access rights changes via a web portal, reducing the use of emailing Word documents by 95% between 18 departments.
- Implemented two-factor authentication on 32 critical systems using hardware tokens, preventing 1.5K unauthorized access requests to sensitive databases.
- Conducted risk assessments on 20 company assets, including software and hardware systems, identified and resolved 2K potential security vulnerabilities in 3 months.

Data Scientist

August 2010 - January 2013

Resume Worded's Exciting Company, New York, NY

- Designed an algorithm that leveraged natural language processing (NLP) techniques to extract structured information from unstructured medical records in real-time, resulting in a 5X reduction in the time needed to process 85K patients' data during onboarding.
- Built a recommender system using collaborative filtering algorithms to recommend personalized care plans for 29 patients based on their disease state and treatment history, increasing physician efficiency by 55%.
- Implemented a machine learning framework capable of detecting anomalies within large volumes of streaming IoT sensor data at millisecond resolution, reducing downtime across power grids, oil, and gas pipelines by up to 75%.

CONTACT

- Denver, OH (Open to Remote)
- · +1-223-912-009
- email@resumeworded.com
- linkedin.com/in/username
- · github.com/resumeworded

SKILLS

Technical:

- Bentley MicroStation (Advanced)
- Autodesk AutoCAD (Experienced)
- VMware
- Puppet
- · Visible Razor

Techniques:

- Regression testing
- MongoDB
- · AWS Cloud Services

Tools:

- · Apache Avro
- JUnit
- · Selenium
- · Debugview
- RegMon
- Don't forget to use <u>Resume</u>
 <u>Worded</u> to scan your resume
 before you send it off (it's free and proven to get you more jobs)

EDUCATION

Resume Worded University

Bachelor of Science Applied Mathematics Boston, MA — May 2009

Awards: Resume Worded Teaching Fellow (only 5 awarded to class), Dean's List 2012 (Top 10%)

OTHER

- · Software Testing Club.
- Member, Software Quality Assurance Forums.